Voices of Civil Rights Project collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series III: Bus Tour Interviews and Events Sound Recordings, 2004-2005
  - Subseries I: Sound Recordings, 2004, 219 sound discs (minidiscs), 79 sound cassettes and 10 microcassettes
    - AFC 2005/015: SR134, 1 minidisc
      - Norma Jean Armstrong interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04
      - Jane VanderVeer interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04
      - Donna Smith interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04
      - James Frykdahl interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04
      - John Cain, Jr., interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04
      - Mary Robinson interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04
      - Curtis Dalton interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04
      - Barbara Ann Brooks interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04
      - A. Miriasiem Barnes interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-04
    - AFC 2005/015: SR135, 1 minidisc
      - Nicole Williams interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Joseph Debro interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Donald Rasmussen interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Estrellita Hudson-Redus interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Lance Cutler interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Claire Wahrhaftig-Isaacs interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Dante Gonzales interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Douglas Robinson interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR136, 1 minidisc
      - Douglas Robinson interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05 (2 of 2)
      - C. Tasmiya King-Miller interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Jessie Cagan interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Steven Miller interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Carolyn Stokes interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Daphne Muse interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Janis Jackson interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Walter Riley interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Annie McKinzie-Dodd interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Beverly Smallwood interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Gregory Brown interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
      - Linda Ricketts interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Oakland, California, 2004-09-05
    - AFC 2005/015: SR137, 1 minidisc
      - Clarence Murray interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26
      - Asberry Butler interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26
      - Phadra Glenn interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26
    - AFC 2005/015: SR138, 1 minidisc
      - Ernest McGowen, Jr., interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26
      - Malaika Adan interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26
      - D'Arcy Hanna interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26
      - Delia Lujan interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26
      - M. J. Khan interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26
    - AFC 2005/015: SR139, 1 minidisc
      - Otis Emanuel interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25
      - Philip Brady interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25
      - Paul Burns interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25
      - Don Whitfield, Sr., interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25
      - Charlie Granger interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25
      - Sadie Roberts-Joseph interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25
      - Dorothy Stepteau interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25
    - AFC 2005/015: SR140, 1 minidisc
      - Andrew Hernandez interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in San Antonio, Texas, 2004-08-27
      - Clarence McGowan interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in San Antonio, Texas, 2004-08-27
    - AFC 2005/015: SR141, 1 minidisc
      - Mary Jefferson Burciaga interviewed by Esther Iverem in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19
      - George Dale interviewed by Esther Iverem in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19
      - John Walker interviewed by Esther Iverem in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19
      - Sarah Ann Dave interviewed by Esther Iverem in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19
      - Katie Daniels interviewed by Esther Iverem in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19
      - Ada Chambers Thomas interviewed by Esther Iverem in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19
      - Charles Lindsey interviewed by Esther Iverem in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19
      - Lawrence Rhodes interviewed by Esther Iverem in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19
      - Paul Campbell interviewed by Esther Iverem in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19
    - AFC 2005/015: SR142, 1 minidisc
      - Lee Eubanks interviewed by Esther Iverem in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19 (2 of 2)
      - Elizabeth Gray interviewed by Esther Iverem in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19
      - Velma Gray interviewed by Esther Iverem in Jackson, Mississippi, 2004-08-19
    - AFC 2005/015: SR143, 1 minidisc
      - Louis Sarabia interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Hobbs, New Mexico, 2004-08-24
      - Eppie Calderon interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Hobbs, New Mexico, 2004-08-24
      - Carol Kaplo interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Hobbs, New Mexico, 2004-08-24
      - Verna Jean Hodge interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Hobbs, New Mexico, 2004-08-24
      - Carl Mackey interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Hobbs, New Mexico, 2004-08-24
    - AFC 2005/015: SR144, 1 minidisc
      - Hilario Romero interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Espanola, New Mexico, 2004-08-30
        See related transcript
      - Roberto Garcia interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Espanola, New Mexico, 2004-08-30
      - Bernardo Pérez interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Espanola, New Mexico, 2004-08-30
      - Ricardo Guzmán interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Espanola, New Mexico, 2004-08-30
        Related transcript
      - Isabel Herson interviewed by Debra Krol in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25
      - Veda Bailey interviewed by Debra Krol in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25
      - Willie Estelle Mellion interviewed by Debra Krol in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25
      - Mary Allen Taylor interviewed by Debra Krol in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25
      - Gail Ray interviewed by Debra Krol in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25
      - Ileana Gómez interviewed by Debra Krol in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25
      - Eunice Paddio-Johnson interviewed by Debra Krol in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2004-08-25
    - AFC 2005/015: SR145, 1 minidisc
      - Darrell Russell interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Fort McDowell, Arizona, 2004-09-02
      - Valerie Lejero interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Fort McDowell, Arizona, 2004-09-02
      - Veronica Jones interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Fort McDowell, Arizona, 2004-09-02
      - Alida Montiel interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Fort McDowell, Arizona, 2004-09-02
    - AFC 2005/015: SR146, 1 minidisc
      - Wendell Baker interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26
      - Victor Washington interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26
      - Michica Guillory interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26
      - Virgie Pink Jenkins-Henry interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26
      - Carole Barasch interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26
      - Paul Matthews interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26
      - Laura Frazier interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26
      - Mildred Nero Taylor interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26
      - Dora Taylor Mosley interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26
      - Charlene Simmons interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Houston, Texas, 2004-08-26
    - AFC 2005/015: SR147, 1 minidisc
      - Willie Young interviewed by Esther Iverem in Philadelphia, Mississippi, 2004-08-20
      - Christine Waldrip interviewed by Esther Iverem in Philadelphia, Mississippi, 2004-08-20
      - James Young interviewed by Esther Iverem in Philadelphia, Mississippi, 2004-08-20
      - William White interviewed by Esther Iverem in Philadelphia, Mississippi, 2004-08-20
      - Luvenia Lampkin interviewed by Esther Iverem in Philadelphia, Mississippi, 2004-08-20
      - D. Lucile Naylor interviewed by Esther Iverem in Philadelphia, Mississippi, 2004-08-20
    - AFC 2005/015: SR148, 1 minidisc
      - Gilbert Martinez interviewed by Debra Krol in Espanola, New Mexico, 2004-08-31
      - Benny Shendo, Jr., interviewed by Debra Krol in Espanola, New Mexico, 2004-08-31
      - Moises Morales, Jr., interviewed by Debra Krol in Espanola, New Mexico, 2004-08-31
      - Josephine Natseway interviewed by Debra Krol in Espanola, New Mexico, 2004-08-31
      - Andres Martinez interviewed by Debra Krol in Espanola, New Mexico, 2004-08-31
    - AFC 2005/015: SR149, 1 minidisc
      - Diana Coleman interviewed by Debra Krol in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
      - Ruth Swart interviewed by Debra Krol in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
      - John Stewart interviewed by Debra Krol in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
      - Barbara Rhine interviewed by Debra Krol in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
      - John Handy, IV, interviewed by Debra Krol in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
      - Allen Feaster interviewed by Debra Krol in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
      - William Pegg interviewed by Debra Krol in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
      - Joyceann Brooks interviewed by Debra Krol in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
      - Lisa Lee interviewed by Debra Krol in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
      - Michael Roosevelt interviewed by Debra Krol in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
      - Tommy Escarcega interviewed by Debra Krol in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
      - Hiram Pittman interviewed by Debra Krol in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
      - D. Stella LeMone interviewed by Debra Krol in Oakland, California, 2004-09-06
    - AFC 2005/015: SR150, 1 minidisc
      - Bill Mitchell interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-10
      - Alphonso Hamilton interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-10
      - Sandra Christmas interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-10
      - Bill Page interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-10
      - Gail Johnson interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-10
      - Anthony Carter interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-10
      - Rudolph Valentino Thompson interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-10
      - Richard Lee interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-10
      - Audrey Quarles interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-10
      - Edward Silas interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-10
      - Myrelean Moore interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-10
    - AFC 2005/015: SR151, 1 minidisc
      - Herzel Maymon interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-11
      - Herzel and Yehudit Maymon interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-11
      - Rickey Madison interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-11
      - Patricia Johnson interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Los Angeles, California, 2004-09-11
    - AFC 2005/015: SR152, 1 minidisc
      - R. B. Cottonreader interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24
      - Warren Deeds interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24
      - Gloria Smith interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24
      - Georgianne Thomas interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24
      - Fenton Golden interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24
      - Birdie England interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24 (2 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR153, 1 minidisc
      - Lillie Kate Benitez interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24
      - Charlotte Walker interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24
      - Dolores Lawson interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24
      - Lorraine Ensley interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24
      - Alma Simmons interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24
      - Ruby Thurmon interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24
      - Mary Curtis Ashong interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24
      - Birdie England interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR154, 1 minidisc
      - Timothy Ahrens interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
      - Bessie Sherrod interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
      - Arthur Slate interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
      - Ethel Tanner interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
      - Julia Roddey interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
      - Joel King, Jr., interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
      - Millie Tanner-Latham interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
      - William Craig interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
      - Elfriede Bennett interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
    - AFC 2005/015: SR155, 1 minidisc
      - Rutha Mae Harris interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
      - Lovye Cochran interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
      - Mardesque Shirley interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
      - Alma Chatmon interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
      - Thomas Chatmon, Jr., interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
      - Randolph Battle, Jr., interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
    - AFC 2005/015: SR156, 1 minidisc
      - Ermer Pondexter interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-26
      - Effie Jones Bowers interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-26
    - AFC 2005/015: SR157, 1 minidisc
      - Curtis Sykes interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-26
    - AFC 2005/015: SR158, 1 minidisc
      - Charles Grider interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-26
      - Clai Hall interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-26
    - AFC 2005/015: SR159, 1 minidisc
      - Emma Bell Lee interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Macon, Georgia, 2004-09-21
      - Betty Troutman Lumpkin interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Macon, Georgia, 2004-09-21
      - Enola Dozier interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Macon, Georgia, 2004-09-21
      - Haley Johnson interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Macon, Georgia, 2004-09-21
      - Jack Ellis interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Macon, Georgia, 2004-09-21
      - Dorothy Vining interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Macon, Georgia, 2004-09-21
      - Annie Ruth Turner interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Macon, Georgia, 2004-09-21
      - Annie Singleton interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Macon, Georgia, 2004-09-21
      - Shirley Hunt interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Macon, Georgia, 2004-09-21
    - AFC 2005/015: SR160, 1 minidisc
      - Lucille Kennedy interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Macon, Georgia, 2004-09-21
      - Jenny Mae Roberts interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Macon, Georgia, 2004-09-21
      - Frances Walker interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Macon, Georgia, 2004-09-21
      - Kenneth Knight interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Macon, Georgia, 2004-09-21
    - AFC 2005/015: SR161, 1 minidisc
      - Ted Ohira interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25
      - Chizuko Ohira interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25
      - Naomi Wilson interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25
      - Katherine Mitchell interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25
      - Sylvia Kobayashi interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25
      - Mary Annie Jackson interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25
      - Gary Shiota interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Little Rock, Arkansas, 2004-09-25 (2 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR162, 1 minidisc
      - John Werthing, Sr., interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09-17
      - Wilbert Bond interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09-17
      - Jessie Mae McNeely interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09-17
      - Cecille Tackett interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09-17
      - Lester Gingold interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09-17
      - Helen Webb interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09-17
      - Willie Shields interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09-17
      - Reuben Williams interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09-17
      - Gloria Anthony interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09-17
      - Walter Crawford interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09-17
      - Robert Kinnard interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09-17
      - Billy Rodgers interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09-17
    - AFC 2005/015: SR163, 1 minidisc
      - James Anderson interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Modesto, California, 2004-09-08
      - Mack Wilson interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Modesto, California, 2004-09-08
      - Tommie Muhammad interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Modesto, California, 2004-09-08
      - Barbara Anderson interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Modesto, California, 2004-09-08
      - Lillie Clark interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Modesto, California, 2004-09-08
      - Karyn Clark interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Modesto, California, 2004-09-08
      - Alicia Hugg interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Modesto, California, 2004-09-08
      - Ineda Keita interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Modesto, California, 2004-09-08
      - Marguerite Dill interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Modesto, California, 2004-09-08
      - Henry Dill interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Modesto, California, 2004-09-08
      - Frankie Greene interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Modesto, California, 2004-09-08
    - AFC 2005/015: SR164, 1 minidisc
      - John Perdew interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
      - Patricia Perry interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
      - Arthur Williams interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
      - Sam Hall interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
      - Willie Thomas interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Albany, Georgia, 2004-09-20
    - AFC 2005/015: SR165, 1 minidisc
      - Roscoe McWilliams interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09-17
      - Georgia Harvey interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09-17
      - Anthony Bell interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09-17
      - Jimmy Morgan interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09-18
      - Jimmy Williams interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09-18
      - Mary Richardson interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09-18
    - AFC 2005/015: SR166, 1 minidisc
      - Janis Fullilove interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09-18
      - Beatrice Prescott Green interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09-18
      - Claudia Butler interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Memphis, Tennessee, 2004-09-18
    - AFC 2005/015: SR167, 1 minidisc
      - Margo Waters interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24
      - Cheri Johnson interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24
      - Kate Gainer interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24
      - Samuel Mitchell interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24
      - Bernard Baker interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24
    - AFC 2005/015: SR168, 1 minidisc
      - Patricia Burkes interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24
      - Narvie Harris interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Atlanta, Georgia, 2004-09-24
    - AFC 2005/015: SR169, 1 minidisc
      - Norman Jones, II, interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
      - Joel Taylor interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
      - Frank Jones, Jr., interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
      - Richard Logan interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
    - AFC 2005/015: SR170, 1 minidisc
      - James Greene interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
      - Sylvia Walker interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
      - Dolvies Coke interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
      - Joyce Birden interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Columbus, Ohio, 2004-09-28
    - AFC 2005/015: SR171, 1 minidisc
      - Marie Britt-Sharpe interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03
      - James Hazelwood interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03
      - Ashanti Hamilton interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03
      - Willie Lovelace interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03
      - Beverly Coleman interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03
      - Kevin Thomas interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03
      - Edward Wood interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03
      - Lauri Wynn interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 2004-10-03
    - AFC 2005/015: SR172, 1 minidisc
      - Eleanor Young Love interviewed by Rita Neubauer in New Albany, Indiana, 2004-10-01
      - Oneita Phillips interviewed by Rita Neubauer in New Albany, Indiana, 2004-10-01
      - Rhoda Temple Morton interviewed by Rita Neubauer in New Albany, Indiana, 2004-10-01
      - Sally Newkirk interviewed by Rita Neubauer in New Albany, Indiana, 2004-10-01
      - Yvonne Grundy interviewed by Rita Neubauer in New Albany, Indiana, 2004-10-01
    - AFC 2005/015: SR173, 1 minidisc
      - Mildred Bolden interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Indianapolis, Indiana, 2004-10-02
      - Nellie West interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Indianapolis, Indiana, 2004-10-02
      - Christine Davis interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Indianapolis, Indiana, 2004-10-02
      - Guy Russell interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Indianapolis, Indiana, 2004-10-02
      - Doris Evans Russell interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Indianapolis, Indiana, 2004-10-02
      - James Boyd interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Indianapolis, Indiana, 2004-10-02
    - AFC 2005/015: SR174, 1 minidisc
      - Perralene Madison interviewed by Rita Neubauer in Detroit, Michigan, 2004-09-30